{
    "subject": "resource/John_Denver",
    "predicate": "property/label",
    "object": "resource/Sony_Wonder",
    "human_readable": "The label of John Denver is Sony Wonder.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8643350005149841,
            "question": "Did John Denver have any collaborations with other artists on the Sony Wonder label?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8370608687400818,
            "question": "What is the significance of John Denver's association with Sony Wonder?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8041357398033142,
            "question": "What label was associated with John Denver?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6718165278434753,
            "question": "Who is John Denver?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6549821496009827,
            "question": "Was John Denver signed to a record label?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5284422039985657,
            "question": "Can you name any artists on the Sony Wonder label?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5022217035293579,
            "question": "What is Sony Wonder known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41807976365089417,
            "question": "What type of music was John Denver known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3904438614845276,
            "question": "Is 'Sony Wonder' a subsidiary of a larger record company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3453713357448578,
            "question": "Were there other famous musicians signed to Sony Wonder?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of John Denver is Sony Wonder.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7862_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'Sony Wonder' a subsidiary of a larger record company?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7862_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of music was John Denver known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7862_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Sony Wonder known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7862_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7862_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7862_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7862_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7862_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7862_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7862_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7862_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7862_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7862_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7862_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: There is no information in the provided context that mentions \"Sony Wonder\" as a label for John Denver. The context does mention labels like RCA and Legacy Recordings, but not Sony Wonder."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}